

ZAKI SADAQATZADA

Learner of Computer Science

PROFILE

A highly efficient, hardworking and talented graduate student from High School and with more than one and half years of extensive theoretical and practical experience in computer science worked as intern at FADAC and thought English Language at DELTA plus teacher at Jambud High School with core teaching skills both computer programs, school's subjects, and English language. Self-oriented and willing to gain new skills and thoughts shortly.

CONTACT



+93765818245



+92 328 398 8607



zakisadaqatzada@gmail.com

EXPERTISE

Core Competencies

- Computer hardware skills
- HTML
- CSS
- Java Script
- Photoshop
- Windows
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Teaching skills
- Teamwork

EXPERIENCE

INTERN

FADAC | July 2021 - December 2022

- As instructor taught Microsoft Office programs including Ms. Word, PowerPoint and Excel including typing skills.
- Repairing both software and hardware of computers in different types and models.
- Learned how to effectively deal with clients and the best way to work in a team, being adaptive and creative at different stages.
- Enough patience on finding the issues and following the solutions.
- I realized how to listen to the grievance of customers and how to properly interact with them to get their acceptance.
- Overall, I was supportive of all the teams in different stages of

ENGLISH INSTRUCTOR

DELTA Educational Center | June 2022 – February 2023

- Taught English language focused on the four main areas of reading, listening, speaking, and writing.
- Learned the teamwork and how to deal with the students all types of claims and issues in a polite and mindful pathway.
- Trying to teach students not only with my English skills but also with my practical behaviors and positive mindset.
- Listening to the students' feedback and providing them with my appropriate solutions for better study.
- Skilled on time management, developing agenda, punctuality and the best way of interactions with students in effective manner.

SCHOOL TEACHER

JAMBUD Boys High School | March 2018 – December 2020

- Taught general subjects of schools for the grads 10 to 12 during my study at the same school.
- Mainly taught Mathematics and Physics.
- I learned of how to be a good teacher the feelings and further dealing with the students' issues and duties.
- I learned how to convey the massage to student in a good way.
- Also, I learned how to motivate student to learn, to try hard and to admire them for their future goals and targets.
- As a teacher how to be friend with the student to get the insight of student freely and make them happy.

EXPERTISE

Personal Competencies

- Presentation Skills
- Plan Developments
- Creating New Procedures
- Academic Writing
- Business Writing
- Interview Skills
- Email Writing
- Making Communities
- Teamwork
- Typing skills

LANGUAGE

- English | Full Fluent
- Persian | Native
- Urdu | Good

REFERENCE

(f) Historical Music

Travelling

Photography

Football

REFERENCE

L

Eng. Naqi | Director of FADAC

Email: alins.100z@gmail.com

Phone/WhatsApp: +93745634243

Address: District #13, Kabul,

Afghanistan

EDUCATION

Information System (IS) @ Kabul University

March 2021 - August 2021.

Due to the conflict in the country, I could not continue my study.

Diploma of English @ Taimuri English Language Academy

March 2023 - February 2024

Diploma in English Language - DEL

Diploma of English @ Star Educational Society

February 2021 – July 2022

Advanced English diploma

Diploma of Web designing (front-end development)

10th oct 2023- 10th January 2024

Global institute of computer and technology

Diploma of Adobe Photoshop (Basic to Advanced)

18th May 2023 - 3rd August 2023

Global institute of computer & technology

ICDL Certificate (Office package)

June-2021

Razi Professional Development Institute

Diploma of High School @ Jambud Boys High School

March 2008 - December 2020

General studies

AWARDS & APPRECIAITONS

- Student fist position award
 Jambud Boys High School | August 2022
- Appreciation Letter
 TELA Academy | January 2024
- Acknowledgement Letter
 DELTA Educational Center | October 2022
- Appreciation letter
 Star Educational Society | March 2022